

Arne Van Den Kerchove arne. vandenkerchove@ student.kuleuven.be arne. vandenkerchove.com +32 473 32 78 71

> Address 33 Dijkstraat Dessel, 2480 Belgium

Arne Van Den Kerchove

Computer Science Student

About Me I am a motivated Computer Science Student at KU Leuven University. I volunteer in multiple non-profit organisations, both in Leuven and in my home town. My field of interest is large and I love to discover new experiences and cultures.

Education

2017 - present, KU Leuven University

Master's Degree in Engineering Sciences: Computer Science (Ongoing)

2014 - present, KU Leuven University

Bachelor's Degree in Informatics (Ongoing)

Professional Experience

2016 - present, Freelance Drupal Webdeveloper

I currently am a self-employed webdeveloper and webdesigner. I use the Drupal CMS to provide personalised websites to my clients.

May 2015, Database Refactoring, Brabantse Apothekers Federatie

Transferring the company's database to a new database management program.

June 2014 - August 2014, Front-end Webdeveloper, GBits Webdevelopement

Designing CSS/HTML templates for the DotNetNuke CMS.

Personal Experience

February 2016 - present, Webmaster, Scientica Leuven vzw

I manage the computer systems, software and website of the overarching student Association Scientica. I am in control of a multi-server system, primarily used for our member database and student course sale system.

2015 - present, Responsible Person Webteam, Wina Leuven vzw

I lead the technical support team of our student association Wina. I am in charge of a team consisting of 12 volunteers.

2014 - 2018, Vice Responsible Person, Youth Red Cross Retie-Dessel

I am a youth leader in my local youth movement. We are an openly accessible youth movement, that combines playing and teaching about First Aid.

July 2016, Sailing Trainee, The Tall Ships Races

I participated in the 2016 Tall Ships Races. This is an international and multicultural sailing regatta. I worked and lived together with people from different countries while sailing from Antwerp to Lisboa.

Communication Skills

- Native Language: Dutch
- Full Professional Proficiency: English, German
- o Minimum Professional Proficiency: French
- o Elementary Proficiency: Spanish, Italian



Arne Van Den Kerchove arne. vandenkerchove@ student.kuleuven.be arne. vandenkerchove.com +32 473 32 78 71

> Address 33 Dijkstraat Dessel, 2480 Belgium

Software Development Skills

Programming

- JQuery

Computer Software

MySQL
LaTeX
HTML
CSS
Git,Gitlab CI
R
Server stack

Other Qualifications

Animator in Youth Work, Flemish Government First Aid Emergency Worker, Belgian Red Cross

Interests

Professional

Artificial intelligence, software design, webdesign and webdevelopment, declarative programming languages, science and engineering.

Personal

Travelling, first aid and Red Cross, books, guitar, biology.